in this lecture I will place text on a
在这次演讲中，我将把课文放在一个
three-dimensional object
三维对象
let's create a 3D queue in inkscape I've
让我们在Inkscape中创建一个3D队列
already created a cube before and will
之前已创建多维数据集，并将
show the basics
展示基本知识
I select the 3D box tool I click and
我选择3D框工具，然后单击
drag from the left corner I've now drawn
从我现在绘制的左角拖动
a small part of the queue to make it fit
队列中的一小部分以使其适合
I drag a front corner to the same place
我把一个前角拖到同一个地方
I can increase the length by dragging
我可以通过拖拽来增加长度
one of the four nodes
四个节点之一
to go the other way I hold shift and
换一种方式，我按住Shift键
drag the opposite corner and to make the
拖动对角，以使
cube higher I hold Ctrl and drag a
立方体更高我按住Ctrl键并拖动
corner I can also prolong from the
转角我也可以延长从
bottom holding Ctrl and I can prolong
底部按住Ctrl键和我可以延长
from the front or from the back holding
从前面或从后面持球
the control key I go to outline preview
Ctrl键我会进入大纲预览
mode by pressing Ctrl y
通过按Ctrl y键进入模式
if I zoom out I see it Place The
如果我缩小，我会看到它放置在
Vanishing points of the three converging
三个收敛的消失点
lines at the same distance using a
相同距离的线条使用
circle
圆
The Vanishing points also have equal
消失点也有相等的
distance to each other
彼此之间的距离
this way you get a uniform Cube if I
这样你就可以得到一个统一的立方体，如果我
bring a vanishing point closer to the
使消失点更接近
cube I will create more perspective
立方体我会创造更多的视角
in the menu above you can also change
在上面的菜单中，您还可以更改
finite converging lines to infinite
有限向无限收敛的直线
parallel lines by clicking on the toggle
通过单击切换按钮来选择平行线
icons
图标
I prefer however to work with three
然而，我更喜欢与三个人一起工作
Vanishing points for realistic results
逼真效果的消失点
and by dragging the little cross I can
通过拖动这个小十字架，我可以
move the cube in 3D space
在3D空间中移动立方体
I will finalize the cube by going to
我将通过以下方式最终确定立方体
path object to path
路径对象到路径
in my layers I see the cube exists of
在我的层中我看到了立方体的存在
six planes if I hold alt I can see which
六架飞机，如果按住Alt，我能看到哪一架
plane corresponds with a path
平面对应于一条路径
I only need the front planes so I delete
我只需要前面的飞机，所以我删除了
the back planes
后部飞机
I call the object Q
我称该对象为Q
I will flip the cube horizontally
我将水平翻转这个立方体
now let's place the text to easily place
现在，让我们轻松地放置文本
the text on the cube planes I will first
立方体平面上的文本我将首先
place the text on a square
将文本放在正方形上
with the rectangle tool I create a
使用矩形工具，我创建了一个
square by holding Ctrl I will duplicate
按住Ctrl键进行方块复制
it twice I select the text tool for my
我两次选择我的文本工具
font I will use Alpha slab 1 which is a
字体我将使用Alpha Screen 1，它是一个
free Google font I click and type
我点击并输入免费Google字体
outside I hold down alt and decrease the
在外面我按住Alt并减少
line height with the arrow up key
带向上箭头键的线高
I will make the text fit the square and
我会让文本适合正方形，
leave the edge visible
让边缘可见
I will also Place text on the other
我还会将文本放在另一个上
squares
小二乘
to easily place the text on the Queue I
轻松将文本放置在队列I上
will cut the text from the squares so I
我会从方块上剪下文本，所以我
select the text in a square and go to
选择正方形中的文本并转至
path difference I will give the pass a
路径差异我会给通行证a
name
名称
I make the background a bit lighter and
我让背景变得淡一点，
I make the cube black
我把立方体变成黑色
to place the text in perspective I go to
将文本放在我去的角度
pathfx
路径fx
from the menu I choose perspective
从菜单中我选择角度
envelope behind type I choose
我选择的类型后面的信封
perspective
透视
I select the node tool and activate
我选择节点工具并激活
snapping
捕捉
when I drag the corner nodes they will
当我拖动角节点时，它们会
snap to the corners of the cube
捕捉到立方体的角
I may think 80 Gray
我可能认为80灰色
next I place outside in pathfx I choose
接下来，我将外部放置在我选择的路径fx中
perspective envelope with the node tool
使用节点工具的透视信封
I place the text finally I place the Box
我放置文本最后我放置盒子
I make the Box 10 Gray
我让盒子10灰色